http://www.versata.com/legal/privacy-statement

You are hereHome » Privacy Statement
Updated: July 15, 2014
Versata respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement describes the ways we collect information from and about you, and what we do with the information, so that you may decide whether or not to provide information to us. By accessing our website, you agree to this Privacy Statement. This is our complete and exclusive Privacy Statement and it supersedes any earlier version.
What this Privacy Statement Covers
This Privacy Statement covers how our company treats personal information, if any, collected and received through our website. Personal information is information that can be used to identify a person that is not in the public domain. Examples include your name, address, e-mail address, and other information not publicly available.
This Privacy Statement does not govern the practices of entities that our company does not own or control, or entities that do not own or control our company or people that our company does not employ or manage.
Our Collection and Use of Personal Information
The information we collect may include your personal information, such as your name, contact information, IP addresses, product and service selections and other things that identify you individually. We may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address and cookies. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. When you visit our website, our server logs your IP address and may collect information such as the time and duration of your visit, and the time and duration of the pages on our website you view. We may track link information to see how you arrived to our website. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information.
Our company may use information that we collect about you to: (i) deliver the products and services that you have requested; (ii) manage your customer relationship and provide you with customer support; (iii) perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others; (iv) communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, or other third parties; (v) develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other websites; (vi) verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions, contests and sweepstakes; (vii) enforce our terms and conditions; (viii) manage our business; note that your information may be provided to our agents, vendors or service providers who perform functions on our behalf; (ix) perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and (x) sell or transfer personal information to third parties for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion.
Disclosing Information to Third Parties
We may disclose the personal information that we collect from you in accordance with the terms of this section. We do not reveal personal information about you to third-parties unless: (i) you request or authorize; (ii) in connection with a company-sponsored event or conference; (iii) the information is provided to comply with the law, enforce an agreement we have with you, or to protect our rights or the rights of others; (iv) the information is provided to our agents, vendors or service providers who perform functions on our behalf; (iv) to address emergencies or acts of God; or (v) is otherwise legally permissible to do so. We may also gather aggregated data about our customers and website visitors and disclose the results of such aggregated information to our affiliates, service providers, advertisers and/or other third parties for marketing or promotional purposes.
Our Security Measures to Protect Information
Our company uses industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving data exchanged between our company and other companies to help ensure its security. This site has security measures in place to help protect information under our control from the risk of accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration or unauthorized disclosure or access. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. If this website contains links to other sites, our company is not responsible for the security practices or the content of such sites.
Cookies, Web Beacons, and Links
Our company websites may use third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements and web usage. This Privacy Statement does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third parties to collect that information.
Cookies. Many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences http://levitrastore.net/. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. You have many choices with regards to the management of cookies on your computer. All major browsers allow you to block or delete cookies from your system. To learn more about your ability to manage cookies, please consult the privacy features in your browser.
Web Beacons. Our company and third parties may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our company’s cookie requirements.
Links. We may create links to other web sites. We will make a reasonable effort to link only to sites that meet similar standards for maintaining each individual's right to privacy. However, many other sites that are not associated with or authorized by our company may have links leading to our site. Our company cannot control these links and we are not responsible for any content appearing on these sites. Since this website does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy practices of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose any personal information to others.
Personal Information Retention
We will retain any personal information only for as long as is necessary to fulfil the business purpose it was collected. We will also retain and use your personal information for as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
International Transfers of Personal Information
Information collected from you may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which our company or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities, and by accessing our sites, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
Your Access to and Updating of Personal Information
Reasonable access to your personal information may be provided at no cost upon request made to our company at the contact information provided below. If access cannot be provided within that time frame, our company will provide the requesting party a date when the information will be provided. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation as to why access has been denied.
Changes to Our Privacy Statement
Our company may amend this Privacy Statement at any time by posting a new version. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Statement periodically as your continued use of this website represents your agreement with the then-current Privacy Statement.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices or concerns of this site, please contact our Privacy Officer at: privacy@verstata.com
